rosinstrument.com 2018-10-10

# 

    	Rosinstrument.com Privacy Policy, Fri Mar 13 03:29:45 GMT 2009
     
    Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use 
    personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy 
    before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the 
    site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These 
    practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only 
    apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. 
    You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to 
    make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be 
    used.
    
    Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web 
    site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies 
    posted at those sites.
    
    Collection of Information
    
    We collect personally identifiable information, like nicknames, email 
    addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information 
    you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only 
    used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it 
    in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
    
    Cookie/Tracking Technology
    
    The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features 
    offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information 
    such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to 
    the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help 
    customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via 
    cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided 
    personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. 
    Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
    
    We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our
    website. These companies may use information (not including your name,
    address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and
    other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of
    interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to
    know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,
    visit sites describing the technology http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html,
    http://www.networkadvertising.org/, http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx.
    
    Distribution of Information
    
    We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies 
    assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) 
    permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent 
    actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating 
    fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these 
    companies for marketing purposes. 
    
    Commitment to Data Security
    
    Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized 
    employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure 
    and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters 
    from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 
    
    Privacy Contact Information
    
    If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you 
    may contact us using the information below:
    
    By e-mail: support@rosinstrument.com 
    
    We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy 
    will be posted.
